Finding aid for the Xavier University committees annual reports, and other material
Xavier University Archives and Special Collections
Xavier University committees annual reports, and other material
1991-2010
Xavier University Archives and Special Collections Phone: 513-745-4821 http://www.xavier.edu/cm/archives
Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). President's Office
6 linear feet (12 boxes)
Annual reports of various Xavier committees submitted annually to the president of the university.
XUA- 11
History of Xavier University committee annual reports submissions
Various Xavier University committees have historically been obligated to report annually to the university president as far as their activities for the academic year. In addition to the annual reports themselves, there is much documentation on the selection of committee members for a given academic year. This documentation gives some insight into the selection process for committee participation.
Scope and Content
This collection spans from 1991 to 2010. Materials included in the collection can include annual committee reports, committee lists (whether official or draft copies), correspondence and other communications. Typically each university committee is described in an annual listing of committees and committee members. Annual reports may or may not be found for an established committee for a given academic year. The length and format for annual reports can vary.
Statement of Arrangement
Materials are arranged in the same general manner as given to the archives from the transferring office. The general order is by academic year. Each year's materials most often includes two folders: one for the primary documentation for that year, the other for various ancillary materials found with the materials. Committee records are generally tabbed in an alphabetical arrangement by name of each committee.
Restrictions on Access
Please contact the Xavier University Archives staff.
Other Finding Aid
An additional finding aid for this collection can be found in the Xavier University Archives Office. This aid specifies which annual reports had been filed by individual committees for a given academic year.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Xavier University President's Office to the archives on June 24, 2013.
Accruals
There may be additions to this collection at a later date.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects:
Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio)--Administration
Organizations/Corporations:
Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). President's Office; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Admissions Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Commencement Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Academic Technology Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). University Discipline Board; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Faculty Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Faculty Development Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Financial Aid and Scholarship Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Library Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Parking Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Board of Undergraduate Studies; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Board of Graduate Studies; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). University Committee on Public Honors; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Budget Review Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Multicultural Student Concerns Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). University Rank and Tenure Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Student Publications Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Core Curricululm Review Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Benefits Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Facilities Planning Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Calendar Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio).College of Arts and Sciences Curriculum Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Institutional Review Board; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). College of Social Science, Health and Education Curriculum Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Ethics/Religion and Society Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). University Committee on the Status of Women; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Williams College of Business Curriculum Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). University Technology Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Grievance Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Academic Assessment and Planning Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Faculty Hearing Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Diversity and Equity Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Marketing Coordinating Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Art Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Web Site Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Sexual Harassment Committee; Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Graduate Administrative Council
Detailed Description of The Collection
- Xavier Committee Annual Reports, 1991-1993 (Box 1)
- Xavier Committee Annual Reports, 1993-1995 (Box 2)
- Xavier Committee Annual Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 3)
- Xavier Committee Annual Reports, 1996-1998 (Box 4)
- Xavier Committee Annual Reports, 1998-2000 (Box 5)
- Xavier Committee Annual Reports, 1999-2001 (Box 6)
- Xavier Committee Annual Reports, 2001-2003 (Box 7)
- Xavier Committee Annual Reports, 2002-2004 (Box 8)
- Xavier Committee Annual Reports, 2004-2006 (Box 9)
- Xavier Committee Annual Reports, 2005-2007 (Box 10)
- Xavier Committee Annual Reports, 2007-2008 (Box 11)
- Xavier Committee Annual Reports, 2008-2010 (Box 12)